Guide to the George B. Dantzig Papers
Stanford University Libraries.
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2006-167
  - OR 341 1972-73 Spring (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - OR 340A: Fall 1977-78 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - OR 340A Midterm 77-78, 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - OR 340A: 1978-79 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - OR340: Final & Solutions 78-79, 1978-1979 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - OR 340A. 1976-77 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - OR 341: Winter 1977-78 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - OR 340A: Dec 1974 Final Exam` (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - OR 299: Independent Study, 3/1974-75 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - CS 234: GBD, 10/8/1974 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - OR 340A: Midterm November 1974 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - OR 340B 74/75, 1974-75 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - OR 340B: Midterm, 1974-75 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - CS 234: Numerical Methods of Optimization J.A. Tomlin, Aut. 1973-1974, 1973-74 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - CS 234: 1979-80 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - CS 234: 1977-78 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - OR 340A, 1979-80 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - CS 234: Midterm-Final 11/18/75, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Population, 1987 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Dikin (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - OR 340A Revised Simplex Method (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - L.C. Prob, I.P. Prob Notes (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Course Evaluations, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - OR 250. (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Introduction to L.P. Simplex Method (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - (Not Labeled) Simplex Method Slides (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - OR 340A: Simplex Algorithm Method, Degeneracy (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - OR 340A Price Interpretation of Simplex Method (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - CS 234 Transportation Network Flow (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - OR 340A Duality Theorems (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - OR 340A Formulating a L.P. Notes/Problems/Old Transp. (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Goney Sets, Infeasability, Theorem Separation, Duality Theorem/Alternative (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - (Not Labeled) Extended Feasbility Line Segment, OR 340 Linear Programming Midterm I (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Old Notes OR 340A, Fall 1976 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - GBD Urgent (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - FME Elim., Feasibility Theorem Duality Theorem Notes, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - (Not Labeled) OR 340A Notes, Slides, and other documents (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Simplex Algorithm Degeneracy, Method (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - OR 340A Fourier-Motzkin Equiv. Systems Feasibility Theorem (Old Notes) (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Introduction Solving Equations Motzkin/Fourier, Infeasibility Theorem Chap. 4 Transparencies (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Chapter 3 Transparencies Formulating A L.P. (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Markov Chain, 1960 Feb (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Inductive Proof of p.1851 The Simplex Method (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Symposium on Combinatorial Problems IBM, 1964 Mar 17-18 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Egervary, E. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - de la Vallee Poussin (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Computing Optimal Distribution of Optimal Defense Rand RM-914, 8/12/1952 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Notes on Linear Program: Part I Gen. Sim. Method for Min. a Linear Form under Lin. Inequal. Restraints, 10 Apr. 1953 (Revised 26 Oct. 1953) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Notes on Linear Program: Part II Duality Theorems, 10 Apr. 1953 (Revised 30 Oct. 1953) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Notes on Linear Program: Part III Computational Algorithm of the Simplex Model, 10 Apr. 1953 (Revised 26 Oct. 1953) (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Simplex Method George B. Dantzig (Handbook of Operation), Nov. 1958 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - A Decomposition Principle for Linear Programs Geo. B. Dantzig, P. Wolfe (P-1544), 11/10/1958 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Computing Tetraethyl Lead Requirements In the Linear Programming Format Dantzig, Kawaratani, Ullman (P-1545), 11/12/1958 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Formulating and Solving Linear Programming (Modern Math for the G.B. Dantzig Engineer, E.F. Beckenbach), Nov. 1958 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - (P) Product Form for Inverse in the Simplex Model (with Or.-Hays), 10/9/1953 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Notes on Linear Program: Part V Alternate Algor. for Rev. Simplex Method using Prod. Form for Inverse, 11/19/1953 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Notes on L.P.: Part XXII Recent Advances in Linear Programming, 4/12/1955 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Hoffman, Alan J. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Notes on L.P.: Part XXII A Production Smooth. Prob., 2/28/1955 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - On the Shortest Route Through a Network P-1345 (G.B. Dantzig), 4/21/1958 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Solving Two Move games with Perfect Information P-1459, 8/11/1958 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - On the Significance of Solving Linear Programming Problems with some Integer Variables P-1486, 9/8/1958 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - A Machine - Job Scheduling Model G.B. Danztig P-1502, 9/30/1958 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Substitute Inverse Method, Oct, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Model Japanese National Railway Water Power System Maeda & Ibaragi - Dantzig, 10/8/1958 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - The Dual of a Transportation Problem is not a Transportation Problem Geo. B. Dantzig P-1532, 10/30/1958 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Notes on L.P.: Part XVI The Problem of Routing Aircraft -- A Mathematical Solution, 9/1/1954 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Notes on L.P.: Part XVII Linear Programming Under Uncertainty, 11/16/1964 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - A Min-Max Criterion for Simplex Method, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Upper Bounds, Secondary Constraints, and Blog Triangularity in L.P. (parts VIII, IX, X), 10/4/1954 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Notes on L.P.: Part XXI On the Min. Cut Max Flow Theorem of Networks, 1/1/1955 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Notes on L.P.: Part XVIII Status of Solution of Large Scale L. P. Problems, 11/30/1954 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Notes on Linear Program: Part IV An Algebraic Proof of MinMax Theorem, Rev. 12/18/1953 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Notes on Linear Program: Part X Block Triangular Systems in Linear Programming, 4/8/1954 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Notes on Linear Program: Part XI Composite Simplex-Dual Simplex Algorithm -- I, 4/26/1954 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Notes on L.P.: Part XIV A Computational Procedure for a Scheduling Problem of Edie, 7/1/1954 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Solution of a Large Scale Traveling Salesman Problem, 8/9/1954 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Notes on L.P.: Part XV Minimizing the Number of Carriers to Meet a Fixed Schedule, 8/24/1954 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Notes on Linear Program: Part VII The Dual Simplex Algorithm, 1/4/1954 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Notes on Linear Program: Part VI RAND Code for the Simplex Method, 1/20/1954 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Notes on Linear Program: Part VIII Variables with Upper Bounds in Linear Programming, 3/22/1954 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Notes on Linear Program: Part IX Secondary Constraints in Linear Programming, 3/30/1954 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Divvy Data (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Misc. Talks - folder 2 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Column Pivot Choice (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Can Leontief and P-Matrices Be Rescaled Positive Definite, November 1983 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - (Not labeled) Polaroid Photographs (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - (Not labeled) Time Zero Supercolor Polaroid Film (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - (Not lableed) Time Zero Supercolor Polaroid Film (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Retirement Issues (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - GBD Retirement, 5/17/1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Linear Programming 2: Theory Implementation (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - (Not labeled) Stanford University Class Roll Book OR340 A, Fall 79-80 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - (Not labeled) Stanford University Class Roll Book CS 234, 78-79 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - (Not labeled) Stanford University Class Roll Book OR340A, 78-79 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - (Not lableled) Stanford University Class Roll Book OR 340A Prof. Dantzig, Autumn 1997 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - GBD- Stanford Employ. Statos, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Personnel File, 1980-1996 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Personnel File, 1965-1979 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Compact City Photographs, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Compact City Material, 1981 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - (Not labeled) Compact City Presentation - Photobook (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - (Not labeled) Compact City Presentation - Photobook (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Memoirs, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Memoirs, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Correspondance, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondance, 1959 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondance, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Early List of Papers by GBD (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - A Model Airforce, Fall 1947 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Conditions for Consitency in a Dynhamic System (Strategic Airforce), Fall 1947 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Eloose Notes (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - (Not labeled) Bracketing to Speed Convergence Illustrated on the Von Neumann Algorithm (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - ASA/IMS Talk - Math Techniques of Program Planning, 12/23/1947 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Outline - Selection of Optimum Military Program Programs, 4/6/1948 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Suggestions of the Classification Problem in Linear Prog., 10/11/1948 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Linear Programming on SEAC Talk ACM Washington D.C., 9/7/1950 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Misc. Talks - Folder 1, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Transparencies (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Interviews with George Datzig (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - 1979 Travel Roy L. Adley (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - The Work and the Life of Dr. Thomas L. Saalty, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - (Not labeled) Misc. Personal, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - New book outline (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - (Not labeled) Misc. Algorithms (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - (Not labeled) George Dantzig Birthday Celebration, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - (Not labeled) George Dantzig Internet Article, 7/10/2000 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Transcript "Military Op0erations Research: Observations on its Past, Present, and Future", 1977 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Papers on Stochastic Programming (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - NSF/Engr Dantzig + Glynn, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - (Not Labeled) Proposal to the NSF on System Theory & OR, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Samples, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Archives, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - (Not Labeled) Planning Under Uncertainty Speech (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - G.B.D. Authobyography, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - GBD Vitae, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Dynamic Equilibrium 82-2 & 82-3, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - History of Mathematics in WWII (Rosser), 1981 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Dantzig/Holling manuscript (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Consumers Energy Services Model North-Holland, Avi-Itzhak, Iusem, GBD, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - FIGURES: Dantzig/Hu/Hoffman (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Case ms/ OPTIMA, 1980 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Abstracts MICOM, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - #116, 121, 133 GBD publ. (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Large-Scale Model, 1/1980 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Optima Publication, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Rio ms: Reprinting for North-Holland, 11/1982 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Reminiscence ms (revised 9/1/82 for MP Bonn, Kort), 1983 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Math Programming Bonn 1982 -- The State of Art, Springer -Verlag, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - #143 (SOL 80-3) Math. Prog. J., 1981 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - #142 SIAM REVIEW Khachian Comments (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Dantzig/Holling manuscript revised May 1977, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - On the Reduction of an...Smaller Linear Program, GBD Submitted to Review of Econ and Stat, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - AMS: Energy manuscript, San Antonio, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - A Note on the Objective Function for the PILOT Model, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - American Scientist #124 (never published), 1976 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Bicentennial Conference on MP (Gaithersburg, Nov. 29, 1976) Keynote speaker, paper, energy (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - DANTZIG/MAIER "Formulating and Solving the Network Design Problem by Decomposition", Transp. Research, 1978 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - DANTZIG/SETHI, "Linear Optimal Control Problems and Generalized Linear Programs submitted to Operations Research, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - 78-6, Are Dual Variables Prices?...", 1978 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - 133 (Letter from the Institute of Animal Resource Ecology), 1977 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - "Discovering Hidden Totally Leontief Substitution Systems", 1977 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - AMS ms: Reminiscencs ms, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - (Not Labeled) Various Papers from the American Association for the Advancement of Sciences, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Compact City - Thomas L. Saaty, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Compact City - Publication permission, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - CC - W. H. Freeman & Co. Publishers, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Freshman Seminar Compact City, Winter 1975 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Integrated Model for Capacity Planning for Manufacturing Systems by Andres Ramos, 8/1992 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Various Papers for the Center for Mathematical Studies in Economics and Management Science, 1981 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Papers and Floppy Disk on Degenerate Methods, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Personal Editor II: Learning (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Various Papers on the Four Color Problem and Modeling, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Image: IBM Printout, 1/30/1986 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Various Papers on the Simplex Method (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - In Our Own Image (with GBD Editing) (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Computer Solution of Linear Programs, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - A Proposed Implementation of Compact City (Student Papers), 1975 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Technical Report SOL 83-20, 12/1983 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - References Bibliographies (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - GBD 85th Birthday Celebration, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Bibliography of L.P. Lists Published in 1949 & later (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Bibliography (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - EPRI- Schurr, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - OptiMacros - Optimal Decisions with Spreadsheet Macros, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Linear Programs and Related Problems by E. D. Nering and A.W. Tucker (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Memoirs 1976 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Sample Portfolio, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Decomposition Research, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Agricultural Speech and Paper, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Air Pollution, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Bibliography (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Compl. Spanning Trees (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Crystalography, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Cycle in graph that minimizes total cost, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - D-step Conjecture, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - A Finite Program Equivalent to an Infinite Program, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Local Optimum of Bilinear form whose 2 sets of variables are subject to linear inequality restraints, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Control & Growth Models, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Drews Progress Reports, 1962 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - D or M-Step Conjecture, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Positive (semi-) definite matrices and mathematical programming (Complementarity), 1965 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Minimum No. of Basis Interchanges (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Notes on L.P.: Part XIX The Fixed Charge Problem, 12/54 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Future Developments in O.R., 1959 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Chemical Equilibrium, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - CC - Chapter 14 Publisher (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - CC - Chapter 15 Publisher (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Bell Labs (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - CC Illustrations (originals) (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Avi-Itzhak Summer 1979/Fall 79 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - How to Zone Yerba Buena for Compact City, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - New Cities, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - 1st Attempts at Manuscript (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - In Our Own Image by George B. Dantzig December 1984, 12/84 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - MA - Compact City Essay (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Compact City Class Papers, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Optimal offer construction in electricity markets (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Figures (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Proposal and Nomination for the Harold Larnder Memorial Prize, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Compact City: Special TIMS issue (W. Cooper), 1973 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - ORSA Compact City Address: Reprint Requests, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Galleys: New Orleans CC Talk (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Harold Stone: Compact City lecture?, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Compact City: Book Corrections (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Avi Itzach (Ref), 1995 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Iglehart (Ref), 1996 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Billera Ref., 1996 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Chandrasekaran Ref., 1997 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Infanger Ref., 1996 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Nazereth (Ref.), 1996 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Per Lindberg (Ref), 1995 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Philbrick (Ref) (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Pollatschek Ref, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Alan Manne (Ref), 1995 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Uri Rothblum (Ref), 1995 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Sengupta (Ref), 1996 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Sethi Ref., 1996 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Tellam (Ref) (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Margret Wright (Ref), 1995 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Misc. Papers and The Linear Programming Problem, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Misc. Papers and Letters, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Corresp. about the Prize, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Guy- Prize, 12/87 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Misc. Papers on Awards and Recognition, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Misc. Articles by Various Authors (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Decision making: Cad, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Misc. Articles on Health (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Misc. Papers on Math. Processes (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Hott, Sharon K. Doctoral Program (Fall, 1973) (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Optimization Under Uncertainty (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - First Draft of Thesis - Ed Klotz (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Other People's Brochures and Background about Portfolio (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - A Build Up Interior Point Method for Linear Programming, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Portfolio Optimization Model (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Compact City - News Writing-Ups, 4/16/1972 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Compact Cirty Clippings and Press Releases, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Compact City: Notices on Book Reviews, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - CC: Book, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Compact City: Group IV, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Compact City: Japanese Translation, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Compact City: Permission to quote CC, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - CC - W.H. Freeman & Co. Publishers, 10/72 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - General Correspondence (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence - Inactive (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - People Interested in Compact CIty (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Compact City - Proposal - NSF, 12/1/1972 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Research Proposal - Compact City Correspondence - NSF, 10/1/1972 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - CAC: Compact City Proposal - NSF, May 1973 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - CC: EPRI, 4/26/1974 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - W. Kaufman - CC, 2/22/1974 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - CC: Rodney, 3/6/1974 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Compact City - Paolo Soleri, 2/21/1973 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - General Correspondence 10-72 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - CC - Lectures, 3/1/1972 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - A Model of Energy Policy Analysis, October 1981 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - The Pilot of Energy-Economic Model for Policy Planning, 10/18/1981 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Notes on Computing Economic Equil. (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - 85-7 #163, 8/13/1988 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - 164-6 84-8, 3/12/1987 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - 168: "Origins of the Simples Method," History of Computing, 7/18/1990 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Bealems; Math Prog. 169, 2/2/1987 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - A first order approach...programming problems, Beale/Dantzig/Watson Mathematical Programming, 2/7/1986 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Copies of correspondence with Von Neumman, 10/1/1947 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - MS impact of lp, 3/5/1990 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - 83-17 Copies GBD/Hoffman/Hu, 11/8/1983 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Dantzig, Llasa ms, June 1985 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Here We Are: An Autobiography, October 1989 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Discussion of a Max problem Von Neumman, 11/15/1947 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Department of Agriculture Seminar on Econ. Models - Paper Delivered, Fall 1948 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Geometrical Procedure for Feasible and Maximum Feasible Solution, 10/11/1947 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Hypothetical AF Model, July 1949 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - GBD Publications (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Dantzig biographical Material/Technical Files, 2/24/1949 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Reminiscences (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Remarks on Bicentennial Conf. on Math Prog... Early role NBS (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - GBD Talk - Living Low, December 1976 (Box 16, Folder 42)
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2007-006
  - Album - Dr. George B. Dantzig 85th birthday celebration, informs, 1999 Nov 8 (Box 1)
  - Album - Some reminisces for George B. Dantzig in honor of His 70th birthday, 1984 November (Box 1)
  - Album - Harvey Prize ceremony, 1985 Jun-Jul (Box 1)
  - Photographs - Taken by Lofti Zadeh, 1984 Nov 10-11 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Photographs - National Academy of Sciences (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Photographs - Dantzig with Gerald Ford (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Photographs - Honorary doctorates (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Photographs - Honorary doctorate - Yale, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Negatives, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence - cards, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Symposium on Mathematical Programming to Honor George B. Dantzig, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2010-101
  - Linear Programming Theory & Implemenatio (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - CS 264, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - CS 264, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - OR 340, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - (Not labeled) Class Materials (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - OR 340, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - OR 340, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Rand (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Security - I, 1941-1942 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - (Not labeled) Compact City File, 35091 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Archiving (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - IBM-Contract, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - IBM Progress Reports, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Curriculum Vitaei George Dantzig (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Manila Envelope, 22381 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Crown Zellerbach Corportatin Annaul Report, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Crown Zellerbach Corportatin Annaul Report, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Automatic Order Processing System, 22883 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Computer Aided Paper Machine Scheduling Project Report, July 1963 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - A Preliminary Proposal for Automatic Order Procsssing System, 22883 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Tibor, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Machine Time Expenses for UAL (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Out-of-Kilter Reference Papers for UAL (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - UAL Technical Discussinos Out-of-Kilter (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - UAL Official Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Yale Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - A Guide for the Donors to the Weizmann Institute of Science (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - IBM Offer (other), 1965 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - U.C., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - GBD: Bonds, Insurance, Payroll, Etc. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Richfield + Other, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Mathematics - Papers to be studied (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Prudential Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Prudential (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Prudential Consulting (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Richfield (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - GBD Misc. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - The Dollar Guide (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Mathematica - Official Correpondence, 1959-1961 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - EIP Ready (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Atlantic Refining Co. Dr. John H. Ramser (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Prudential Preliminary (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Mathematics - Completed Papers, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Mathematica - Navy Proposal - Inventory Control; Math Programming Data Processing, 21796 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Brewery (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Mathematica - Material in Preparation for Harlan, 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Mathematica, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - CEIR - Correspondence (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Carnation, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Misc. (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - 143, October 1998 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 144, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 2)